<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Howl Social Blog</title>
        <link>https://docs.howl.social/blog</link>
        <description>Howl Social Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public Beta Debrief]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.howl.social/blog/public-beta-debrief</link>
            <guid>public-beta-debrief</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[If you took part in our Beta test, then thank you!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you took part in our Beta test, then thank you!</p><p>Without all our testers, getting to mainnet would be taking us a lot longer.</p><p>We were blown away by the scale of response - thanks to everybody that had feedback, feature suggestions or helped out in some way.</p><p>Again, like last time, we have some numbers.</p><ul><li>9.42k unique users took part in the testnet</li><li>1,538,091 HOWLx (testnet HOWL) was claimed</li><li>All our documentation challenges were completed</li></ul><p>However, this time there were also some snags - which makes sense, as we get closer to mainnet.</p><ul><li>2 severity 1 bugs</li><li>8 minor bugs</li></ul><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="whats-next---the-road-to-mainnet">What's next - the road to mainnet<a class="hash-link" href="#whats-next---the-road-to-mainnet" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>So what does this mean?</p><p>Well, we have some windows to mend, and then we will run either a closed Beta2 net, or a final open test before we go to mainnet.</p><p>This has pushed our timings back by a couple of weeks, but not by a massive amount.</p><p>Thanks to everybody for their interest in the project and we'll have more updates soon!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>beta</category>
            <category>testing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public Beta Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.howl.social/blog/public-beta-challenges</link>
            <guid>public-beta-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Here are the $HOWL public beta challenges!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here are the $HOWL public beta challenges!</p><p><strong>All challenges start after claim begins. This is targeted for Wednesday 7th September (2022-09-08) at 0900UTC.</strong></p><p><strong>All challenges end on Wednesday 14th September (2022-09-12) at 1300UTC.</strong></p><p><strong>For challenge 1.1. YOU NEED TO ALREADY BE IN THE AIRDROP TO BE ELIGIBLE</strong>. To check this, go to the airdrop claim site. You should be able to see <code>&lt;your-address&gt; can claim X HOWL</code> after connecting your wallet. If you are not eligible, you will see <code>&lt;your-address&gt; was not eligible for the Howl airdrop</code>.</p><p>Some challenges will require the team to calculate who won, so winners may not be announced for several days afterward.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="check-eligibility-and-claim">Check eligibility and claim<a class="hash-link" href="#check-eligibility-and-claim" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>Use the <a href="https://testnet-claim.howl.social/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Airdrop claim tool</a> to check your eligibility and claim.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="challenges">Challenges<a class="hash-link" href="#challenges" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>The challenges are:</p><ol><li><strong><em>Posting Challenge</em></strong> for Howl Genesis users:<ol><li>For every HOWL post you make, you will be awarded 1:1 additional HOWL tokens up to 50 extra tokens.<ol><li>i.e. if you already are eligible for 50 HOWL, you can earn 50 more, for a total of 100.</li><li><strong>NOTE:</strong> <em>only addresses already in the airdrop are eligible for the additional HOWL</em>[0]</li></ol></li></ol></li><li><strong><em>Documentation</em></strong>. Submit a pull-request with your guide to <a href="https://github.com/howlsocial/howldocs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://github.com/howlsocial/howldocs</a> in order to claim these bounties<!-- -->[1]<!-- -->:<ol><li>Getting started with HOWL guides (only 1 guide needs writing for each):<ol><li><strong>Claiming:</strong> <del>How to claim your airdrop - Accepted PR = 500 HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li><li><strong>Create user:</strong> <del>Create a DENS name, set a primary alias. Include how to update and burn if necessary - Accepted PR = 1k HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li><li><strong>Connecting:</strong> <del>Connect wallet to HOWL, connect DENS alias, add HOWL contract to Keplr - Accepted PR = 1k HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li><li><strong>Posting and staking</strong>: <del>how to create a post, how to stake to others’ posts - Accepted PR = 1k HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li><li><strong>Find users to follow:</strong> <del>how to find users, navigate hashtags and reply to posts - Accepted PR = 1k HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li><li><strong>DAOs:</strong> <del>How to post as a DAO, how to reference DAO props etc within HOWL - Accepted PR = 1k HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li><li><strong>Howl Pay:</strong> <del>How to send one-off payments. How to subscribe, how to see your subscribers and those you are paying - Accepted PR = 1k HOWL</del> <strong>CLAIMED</strong></li></ol></li></ol></li></ol><p>Notes on challenges:</p><ul><li>[0]<!-- --> once again - this is only open to users already eligible for the airdrop. If you’re not eligible, you will earn nothing by posting, though you’re welcome to try the app and help us test :)</li><li>[1]<!-- --> note that a bounty will only be paid on an accepted pull-request. For now we’re looking for guides in English, and there may be future bounties for translations of those, once we have high-quality guides. <em>ONLY ONE BOUNTY WILL BE PAID FOR EACH GUIDE</em>.</li></ul><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="bug-bounties">Bug Bounties<a class="hash-link" href="#bug-bounties" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>As in the Public Alpha, the Howl team reserve the right to offer discretionary bounties for:</p><ul><li>Bugs (~2k HOWL available for serious bugs)</li><li>Exploits (~4k HOWL available for an exploit)</li><li>Social engineering of the DAO</li></ul><p>To report a bug or an exploit you’ve found, use the <code>public-beta-bugs</code> channel on Discord.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>beta</category>
            <category>testing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public Alpha Debrief]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.howl.social/blog/public-alpha-debrief</link>
            <guid>public-alpha-debrief</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Thanks to everybody that took part in the Public Alpha.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to everybody that took part in the Public Alpha.</p><p>We got lots of actionable feedback, and have been busy working on new features ready for mainnet - we'll have some news on that soon.</p><p>Some high-level numbers, for the curious:</p><ul><li>1,061 users took part in the challenges</li><li>6/11 ended up being claimed or completed</li><li>20,500 $HOWL in rewards were claimed</li></ul><p>Since then, we've been getting ready for some final testing and kicking the tyres on the final application.</p><p>We're super stoked to share what we've been working on with you all!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>alpha</category>
            <category>testing</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>